[
    {
        "question": "Batman is the alter-ego for which billionaire playboy?",
        "answer_A": "Bruce Wayne",
        "answer_B": "Thomas Wayne",
        "answer_C": "Bill Gates",
        "answer_D": "Michael Keaton",
        "correct" : "Bruce Wayne"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the official creator of Batman?",
        "answer_A": "Bob Kane",
        "answer_B": "Bruce Wayne",
        "answer_C": "Tim Burton",
        "answer_D": "Christopher Nolan",
        "correct" : "Tim Burton"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was the film 'Batman' by Tim Burton released? HINT: Jack Nicholson",
        "answer_A": 1992,
        "answer_B": 1989,
        "answer_C": 1985,
        "answer_D": 2005,
        "correct" : 1989
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the mastermind behind Protocol 10 in 'Batman: Arkham City' video game?",
        "answer_A": "Ra's al Ghul",
        "answer_B": "Hugo Strange",
        "answer_C": "Mister Freeze",
        "answer_D": "The Penguin",
        "correct" : "Ra's al Ghul"
    },
    {
        "question": "What villain does Jim Carrey portray?",
        "answer_A": "The Joker",
        "answer_B": "The Riddler",
        "answer_C": "The Scarecrow",
        "answer_D": "The Penguin",
        "correct" : "The Riddler"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happened to Batman's parents?",
        "answer_A": "Nothing (they are still alive) ",
        "answer_B": "They work for the joker",
        "answer_C": "They died",
        "answer_D": "They went on vacation",
        "correct" : "They died"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Batman's main enemy?",
        "answer_A": "Riddler",
        "answer_B": "Joke man",
        "answer_C": "Harley Quinn",
        "answer_D": "The Joker",
        "correct" : "The Joker"
    },
    {
        "question": "In What Vehicle Does The Joker Escape The Bank Robbery in one of the 'Dark Knight' movies?",
        "answer_A": "An ambulance",
        "answer_B": "A school bus",
        "answer_C": "A fire truck",
        "answer_D": "A tank",
        "correct" : "A school bus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What super villain once broke Batman's back, leaving him crippled and wheelchair-bound?",
        "answer_A": "Bane",
        "answer_B": "Joker",
        "answer_C": "Killer Croc",
        "answer_D": "R`as Al Ghul",
        "correct" : "Bane"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Batman villain lost his beloved wife Nora to a terminal illness?",
        "answer_A": "Scarecrow",
        "answer_B": "Two-Face",
        "answer_C": "Mr. Freeze",
        "answer_D": "The Penguin",
        "correct" : "Mr. Freeze"
    }

]
